Sanjeev Bhasin is seen trading 140 points higher.
Welcome the year. Hello,
tell me like a machine, where is the focus and trend of the wicket on the first
day. I
think your writing is on the table right now. If
not today, then tomorrow you will fast for 15 days.
And the momentum in the industry is good because
the data, macro data is gold.
Corporate results, you have seen from it.
HDFC Bank will come up
with the best profit saver on the 17382. And
today I will give you its large cap. So in the last step,
I will just do it
in Reliance HDFC Bank. Maruti, today I will
give you news that Maruti will
invest Rs 18,000 crore in the next five years
and will sell 10 lakh vehicles and that Naveen look at
the Vijay Upper Zomato, that multiple send
food to homes. Over ten five year
multiple Maruti, so if you have this running plant, then
my first pick is unquestionably
Maruti 73 ₹100. Take vacancy vision, if
you want to sell them in the next year, then
you can imagine vision 7373 Pradesh.  I
take Maruti stop loss of 71827 660
second buy way Kaya HiC
Jhalawar which I am very bullish on Vikram Auto
Centre good record also Share & General
Insurance World Mobile 1540 42
take stopped for 1505 target
more than 90 update which if it does not run today but in
second you midcap banks will definitely run you
just do Bandhan Bank RBI and IDFC
first change is already visible in Bandhan
you have target of 314 1511 325 Chowkpur it will
go to 345 in the month of July Bandhan RBL Bank
IDFC year and 22 midcap IT will be the
best performer in the year internship TDS
let's see good momentum man in front of you